Privacy policy
==============

* * *

BeePass VPN (“**BeePass**”, “**we**”, or “**us**”) is committed to protecting the privacy and confidentiality of any personal information which you may provide, or that we may obtain from you, when you use our website, our VPN services, or otherwise correspond with us.

As a provider of a service aimed at increasing your privacy at the same time as helping you bypass Internet censorship, we aim to collect the minimal amount of data required to provide you with a reliable and an optimal service. This often leads to difficult questions over the data we need to collect and the performance of our service. The purpose of this privacy policy (the “**Policy**”) is to inform you of BeePass’s privacy practices and policies, including:

* how and why BeePass collects your personal information;
* how BeePass intends to use your personal information;
* with which parties BeePass may share your personal information; and
* to provide you with contact information should you have questions or concerns about BeePass’s practices.

This Policy is designed to comply with applicable privacy legislation in Canada, including the _Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act_ (**PIPEDA**). We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully.

By using our website, using our VPN services or directly contacting us by any means of correspondence, you are agreeing to the terms of this Policy and consenting to our policies and practices for the collection, use, storage and disclosure of personal information.

Overview of our privacy practices
---------------------------------

Our privacy practices are summarized here. Under this Policy, BeePass:

1. collects personal information when you use our VPN service, our website, make inquiries and in the course of delivering our services;
2. shares this information with third party service providers (including Amazon, Google, Sentry, and Telegram) for the purposes of administering, supporting our website and services and for feedback and crash report monitoring;
3. collects, uses and discloses this information to provide our products and services;
4. except as set out in (2) & (3), does not share your personal information with third parties without your consent unless authorized or required by law, as part of the sale of a business or as disclosed to you when the information is collected;
5. stores your information with trusted third parties in different regions across the globe, depending on where you access or use our services.
6. retains your personal information in compliance with our legal obligations and only as long as necessary for the purposes for which it was collected;
7. allows you to withdraw your consent to the collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information at any time;
8. mitigates the risk and impact of potential harms involved in the disclosure of personal information through the adoption of reasonable physical, technical and organizational procedures appropriate to the sensitivity of the data in an effort to safeguard the personal information you provide to us; and
9. provides you with updates if there are any changes to this Privacy Policy and our privacy practices through announcements on our website.

Further information with respect to our privacy practices is set out below.

What Information Do We Collect?
-------------------------------

We maintain information relating to our customers and their orders based upon information provided by you. Information is collected in placing orders and in the course of delivering our services. Only personal information that is reasonably necessary is collected. Types of information collected includes registration information, website usage, third party, and other information. The information we collect comes directly from you, our service providers or the website or is information relating to the delivery or performance of our services.

### Account Information

We do not require registration to use our BeePass VPN services. Depending on how you choose to access our services, we collect the following:

* access via BeePass Email Bot: your email address
* access via BeePass Telegram Bot: your Telegram ID or Telegram username, and any other information you provided on your public Telegram account, including your mobile phone number, profile name, profile picture and about information.

### Feedback and Crash Reports

Since BeePass VPN is built for circumvention, there might be situations where we need more information about the user's context to troubleshoot and/or improve BeePass VPN. This is why BeePass VPN allows users to send feedback from the app. We recommend not including personally identifiable information, but if you would like our team to follow up with you or help troubleshoot an issue, you can share your email address or Telegram username through the in-app feedback form. If BeePass VPN crashes or a fatal exception occurs, or if you manually send feedback through the BeePass VPN app, the information listed below will be shared with us:

* Unique identifier Device ID. This ID is randomly generated client-side and does not map to Android unique device identifier.
* Country the user is connected from.
* Date and time of crash / exception and up to 100 prior events, i.e. a user opening the ‘About’ section of BeePass VPN
* Statically compiled exception messages
* Operating system name and version
* Phone model (if applicable)
* App start time
* Browser
* Architecture
* BeePass VPN version and build number

### Usage Information of BeePass VPN Service

We collect your usage data such as the hourly number of bytes transferred when you use our services and the country of origin you are connecting from. We will **not** collect the websites you visit, services you access or your online activity, your IP address assigned to you by your internet service provider.

### Usage Information of BeePass VPN Website

Our website uses "cookies", a technology that installs information on a website user's computer to permit the website to recognize future visits using that computer. This information may include the date and time you access the website, the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to the website, the IP address assigned to you by your Internet service provider, the operating system and browser you are using and any information accessed on the website. Cookies enhance the convenience and use of the website. For example, the information provided through cookies is used to recognize you as a previous user of the website, to track your activity at the Website in order to respond to your needs, to offer personalized web page content and information for your use, and to otherwise facilitate your website experience. You may choose to decline cookies if your browser permits, but doing so may affect your use of the website and your ability to access certain features of the website.

### Other Information

We may collect personal information from you when you make inquiries about our products and services, request assistance through our customer service department or when you voluntarily subscribe to a BeePass service or newsletter.

Third Parties
-------------

Our website and email messages sometimes contain hypertext links to the websites of third parties. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other web sites. Linked web sites are maintained by third parties. Such links are provided for your convenience and reference only. BeePass does not operate or control, in any respect, any information, software, products or services available on such third party web sites. The inclusion of a link to a website does not imply any endorsement of the services or the site, its contents, or its sponsoring organization.

What Do We Use Your Personal Information For?
---------------------------------------------

BeePass collects and uses personal information that you provide or that we collect through your use of our website, our products and services or from the emails we send for the following purposes:

* To provide you your access key to use our services;
* To protect our services and BeePass against and adversaries trying to block or disrupt our services;
* To assess the performance of our networks and optimize resources to improve our services to you;
* To provide customer service and support to you;
* To contact you in connection with your account and your inquiries;
* To administer our website, user account(s) and to manage the emails that we send;
* As permitted by, and to comply with, applicable laws and regulations;
* To protect you, our customers and us against fraud;
* To notify you in connection with any changes or updates to our services or this Policy; and
* Other purposes permitted by law.

How Do We Store Your Personal Information?
------------------------------------------

We currently store and process your personal information and other content you provide to us on servers hosted by third parties. In some circumstances, your personal information may be stored, processed, shared or otherwise used on servers belonging to other third party service providers located within or outside of Canada, including those in the Australia, Brazil, France, Germany, Korea, the Netherlands, Norway, the United States or to other trusted third parties based in other countries. You should be aware that many countries do not afford the same legal protection to personal information as is provided in Canada. Our service providers are only permitted to store, process and access your personal information, and are not otherwise authorized to collect, use or disclose your personal information, except in accordance with the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy or as required by applicable law. However, it is possible that foreign governments, courts, law enforcement or regulatory agencies may be able to access your personal information under foreign laws.

By using our Services or otherwise providing us with personal information, you agree to the transferring of your personal information outside of Canada in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable data protection laws and regulations.

When users request an access key, their information (email address and/or Telegram ID) is stored in a database server that is encrypted.

When users reach out for support through Telegram bot, Telegram has access to their Telegram ID. We also store this information as part of our conversation with the user to be able to track and reach out to users in the future. This data is stored in an encrypted database.

When users reach out for support through email. We store their email address as part of our conversation with the user to be able to track and reach out to users in the future. This data is stored in an encrypted database.

When users send feedback through the app, the information is stored in an encrypted database.

We store your personal information for only as long as is needed to carry out the purposes set out in this Policy. Should you elect to unsubscribe from use of our services, we will hold your information for seven days before it is completely removed from our systems.

Do We Disclose Any Information To Outside Parties?
--------------------------------------------------

We will keep personal information that you provide to us private, and will disclose such personal information only in accordance with this Policy.

BeePass does not sell, rent, or lease to third parties any personal information it collects from you. BeePass may disclose or share personal information with its authorized employees, agents, affiliates, service providers and legal representatives for the purposes described in this Policy. We may also disclose personal information to third parties when necessary to provide a product or service that a person orders from such third party when responding to offers provided by us. We also share your personal information with service providers such as Google for web analytics, use of the Google Play store and Google Firebase debugging services where you are using the BeePass VPN system, Amazon Web Services if you access our services by way of the BeePass Email Bot, Telegram if you access our services by way of the BeePass Telegram Bot, and Sentry to address any feedback or crashes you are experiencing with our services.

If BeePass is involved in the sale or transfer of some or all of its business, then BeePass may disclose your personal information in connection with the transfer or sale but will require the acquiring organization to agree to protect the confidentiality of your personal information in a manner that is consistent with this Policy.

We will not otherwise share your personal information with third parties without your consent, unless authorized or required by law or as disclosed to you when the information is collected (including in this Policy). BeePass may disclose your personal information to a government institution or agency that has asserted its lawful authority to obtain the information or where BeePass has reasonable grounds to believe the information could be useful in the investigation of an unlawful activity, or to comply with a subpoena or warrant or an order made by a court, person or body with jurisdiction to compel the production of information, or to comply with court rules regarding the production of records and information, or to protect the BeePass’s rights and property.

To learn more about the outside parties we work with, please check out the following:

Amazon Web Services: [https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/data-privacy-faq/](https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/data-privacy-faq/)

Telegram: [https://telegram.org/privacy#6-bot-messages](https://telegram.org/privacy#6-bot-messages)

Google: [https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en-US](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en-US)

Sentry: [https://sentry.io/security/](https://sentry.io/security/)

Firebase: [https://firebase.google.com/support/privacy](https://firebase.google.com/support/privacy)

BeePass Default Server
----------------------

When using the default server we can’t guarantee that all information about your internet traffic will be fully private. When connecting to a website using TLS (https) the content you are sending and receiving will be encrypted, however the domain name of the website you are connecting to could be seen by someone with FULL access to your network, like your internet service provider since they can connect to BeePass and access the same key your device will use to encrypt your requests. When connecting to a website not using TLS (http) the full content you are sending and receiving **could** be seen by someone with FULL access to your network.

By using the default server you acknowledge this risk. If you’re concerned we recommend requesting a different server from our Telegram or email bot.

How Do We Protect Your Privacy?
-------------------------------

We keep the personal information we collect about you confidential in accordance with this Policy and have adopted reasonable physical, technical and organizational procedures appropriate to the sensitivity of the data to safeguard the personal information you provide to us. Notwithstanding these measures, no collection, storage or transmission of information over the Internet on websites or otherwise can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and therefore we cannot ensure, warrant or guarantee the security of any such information.

You can find BeePass/Outline's security audit reports [here](https://support.getoutline.org/s/article/Security-and-privacy?language=en_US).

Verifying And Amending Your Personal Information
------------------------------------------------

Subject to certain exceptions prescribed by law, you will be given reasonable access to your personal information held by us and you may request that your personal information be corrected or updated. Please e-mail our Privacy Officer at [support@beepassvpn.com](mailto:support@beepassvpn.com) and we will assist you. You may be required to put your request in writing to confirm your request and identity. It is your responsibility to notify us of any changes to your personal information, including contact information, so we can contact you and inform you about updates to this Policy and any other relevant information with respect to your account and use of our products and services.

Consent
-------

By providing us with your personal information, you consent to the collection, use, storage and disclosure of personal information for the purposes identified in this Policy.

You may withdraw your consent to the collection, use, storage and disclosure of personal information about you at any time. To do this, please contact us by email at: [support@beepassvpn.com](mailto:support@beepassvpn.com). Please note that withdrawal of your consent to the collection, use, disclosure and storage of personal information may result in you being unable to continue to use our services.

Privacy Policy Changes and Updates
----------------------------------

From time to time, we may need to update this Policy or our privacy practices. We will let you know by posting changes on our website. Changes will be effective at the time of posting. It is your responsibility to review our website for any changes and your continued use of our services after the effective date constitute your acceptance of such changes.

This Privacy Policy was last updated on June 29, 2023.

Questions?
----------

If you would like more information about this Policy or the personal information collection, use, storage and disclosure policies and practices of BeePass, including in respect of our policies and practices with respect to service providers outside Canada, please contact our Privacy Officer by e-mail at: [support@beepassvpn.com](mailto:support@beepassvpn.com).

Please let us know your questions or concerns and we will do our best to help you.
